Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to Reel Tapes, 1961-1984
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to Reel Tapes, 1961-1984
Mus. Arc. 1.4
Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1941-1993
15 boxes ( 205 reels of audio tape, 5 LPs, 9 CDs )
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
The collection contains 155 reel to reel tapes featuring performances either by Mikhashoff or of his music, 31 reels that do not contain performances or works by Mikhashoff, and 19 reels containing tape parts to accompany performances. Five LP sound recordings and nine compact discs are also included in the collection.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the estate of Yvar Mikhashoff, 1993.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternative Form Available
The reels in the first and fifth series of the collection containing performances or compositions by Mikhashoff were digitally reformatted in 2015. The funds for the reformatting were generously supplied by the Yvar Mikhashoff Trust for New Music.
The reformatted contents were transferred to a hard drive that is stored with the collection. Preservation wav files were created to match the original reel faces. Production master files (wav) were created to match musical works or other segments of the contents and service copy files (mp3) were created from the production masters.
Biographical Note
Yvar-Emilian Mikhashoff was born Ronald MacKay in Troy near Albany, New York in 1941. He began piano studies with Betty Weir and Stanley Hummel in Albany. At the Eastman School of Music in 1959, he first took a major in composition and cello, then changed to piano studies with Armand Basile. In the 1961 academic year, he studied piano at the Juilliard School in New York City. He also had a career as a ballroom dancer from 1962-1965.
In 1964 Mikhashoff entered the University of Houston for studies in piano with Albert Hirsh. He earned a B.M. in 1967 and continued with graduate study in composition with Elmer Schoettle and obtained his M.M. in 1968. It was during this period that MacKay adopted his grandfather's name, Mikhashoff.
Receiving a Fulbright scholarship in 1968, he studied the music of the French Impressionists with Nadia Boulanger. After his return to the United States, Mikhashoff entered the University of Texas at Austin as a doctoral candidate in composition and studied with Hunter Johnson, Kent Kennan, Janet McGaughey and Karl Korte. He earned a Doctor of Musical Arts degree with a major in composition and a minor in literature in August 1973 and founded the Cambiata Soloists ensemble. In the fall of 1973 Mikhashoff was appointed Assistant Professor in the Music Department at the State University of New York at Buffalo. Based in Buffalo until his death in 1993, Mikhashoff had an international performing career which led him to promote new music and American music around the world.
Mikhashoff had a genius for programming, a talent he utilized extensively while organizing many festivals and broadcasts of new music throughout the world, including his work at the Almeida Festival in London and the Holland Festival. Mikhashoff co-founded the North American New Music Festival in 1983 with Jan Williams and remained a co-director until his death. He commissioned works from such notable composers as John Cage, Lukas Foss, Otto Luening, Poul Ruders, James Sellars, Christian Wolff, and many others. One of his most notable commissioning projects occurred in 1982 when he commissioned or solicited new tangos for solo piano from an international array of more than 80 composers. Mikhashoff also edited publications of music, including works by Henry Cowell, Lejaren Hiller, Conlon Nancarrow, and Virgil Thomson. He recorded on the New Albion, Mode, RCA Victor, CRI, and Spectrum record labels. Yvar Mikhashoff's support of contemporary music continues today through the Yvar Mikhashoff Trust for New Music which was created by his estate to support composers and performers of new music.
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains 155 reel to reel tapes featuring performances either by Mikhashoff or of his music, 31 reels that do not contain performances or works by Mikhashoff, and 19 reels containing tape parts to accompany performances. An additional 5 LP sound recordings and 9 compact discs are included in the collection. The collection has been dated based upon the content of the reels containing Mikhashoff performances and works.
The contents represent a portrait of Mikhashoff's career, not only as pianist and composer, but also as a concert programmer. He had great enthusiasm for exploring different musical themes, including tangos, waltzes, and various eras and styles. This collection contains many examples of Mikhashoff's own spoken word descriptions of the music he was performing.
The container list descriptions are based on the original inventory, which presumably relied upon external sources such as container labels, not auditioning. Reformatting the tapes reveals many details that were previously not known, such as spoken word introductions, changes in program contents, and even blank tapes. The reformatted digital files are listed for tapes in Series I and V to provide some indication of how the files may match the listed contents.
Arrangement
The collection is in five series:
I. Reel to reel tapes with Mikhashoff as performer or composer
II. Reel to reel tapes of accompanying tape parts for performances
III. Reel to reel tapes without Mikhashoff as performer or composer
IV. Long playing and compact disc recordings
V. Reel to reel tapes added from other University at Buffalo sources with Mikhashoff as performer or composer
Container List
- Reel to reel tapes with Mikhashoff as performer or composer, 1961-1984, I.; Item 1-123
  These recordings date back to Mikhashoff's days as an undergraduate student and extend forward into his career on the international stage, including performances in Aspen, Houston, Austin, Albany, New York, Buffalo, New York City, Chicago, The Netherlands, Denmark, and Norway.
  In order as previously processed which is chiefly chronological, with undated items, represented by a range of dates, at the end of the sequence.
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 001, 1961-07-07/1961-08-17, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Aspen 1961 - Hennagin, Copland, Brahms Performers: Ronald MacKay, piano; Toni Rapport, violin; William Maynard, clarinet; Robert Kogan, cello; and Dave Martin, baritone Recording location: Aspen, Colorado Recorded on both sides: Side 2 starts with Copland Variations Contents stated on original container inserted. Requires checking: 1st work Copland piano variations -- 2nd work is Brahms - 3rd work is probably Hennagin's Three inventions - 4th work for cello, clarinet, piano -- 5th work to be identified Derivative files created: 5 (Box 1, Item 1)
    7.5 ips
    Contents: Hennagin: Children's pieces -- Theme, variations, finale -- Recitative and aria -- Three inventions; Copland: Piano variations; Brahms: Six songs from the Magelone
    Digitized copies:
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_001_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_001_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_001_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_001_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_001_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_001_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_001_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_001_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_001_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_001_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_001_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_001_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 002, 1964, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: Dances for Davia Performers: Mikhashoff, piano and Amy, Hunter Winn, flute; or Jay Hersher, flute and John Newell, piano Recording location: Unknown location Performance information in pencil on back of container does not match program used as label on front of container which is for a 19 November 1976 concert at Baird Recital Hall with Jay Hersher, flute and John Newell, piano. Requires checking: 1st track: Dances for Davia -- 2nd track - Solo flute, perhaps incomplete piece and flutist practicing, including excerpts -- 3rd track: song for soprano and piano (Hungarian) -- Recording of "Grenada" playing with people talking -- Records playing, including Vaughn Meader as Kennedy -- Flutist rehearsing -- Flutist rehearsing Derivative files created: 7 (Box 1, Item 2)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: Dances for Davia
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_002_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_002_02am.wav, ubmu0001_4_002_03am.wav, ubmu0001_4_002_04am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_002_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_002_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_002_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_002_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_002_03-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_002_04-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_002_04-02pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_002_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_002_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_002_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_002_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_002_03-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_002_04-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_002_04-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 003, 1965-05-uu, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1965 Junior Recital UH Debussy and Ravel Performers: Ronald MacKay, piano; Lukas Foss, conductor; Phyllis Curtin, soprano; Cleveland Orchestra Recording location: University of Houston Recorded on both sides; side 2 begins with Ives; speed indicated as 7 3/4, presumably a mistake for 7 1/2 Signed Ronald MacKay; Printed program attached; The recordings of the Ives and Foss works are from a radio broadcast of the 1964 performance with the Cleveland Orchestra Requires checking: Gaspard de la nuit divided over 2 tracks: 3-4. Derivative files created: 8 (Box 1, Item 3)
    Contents: Debussy: Preludes (selection of 8); Ravel: Prelude -- Gaspard de la nuit; Ives: From the steeples and the mountains -- Over the pavements -- The unanswered question; Foss: Time cycle
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_003_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_003_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_003_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_003_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_003_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_003_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_003_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_003_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_003_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_003_02-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_003_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_003_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_003_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_003_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_003_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_003_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_003_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_003_02-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 004, 1965-05-24, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1965 Junior Recital (UH) May 24 Performers: Ronald MacKay, piano; Albert Hirsh, piano; Amy Hunter, flute; David Herbert, oboe; Willo Brotherton, clarinet Recording location: University of Houston, Ezekiel W. Cullen Auditorium Printed program attached Derivative files created: 5 (Box 1, Item 4)
    Contents: Debussy: Preludes (selection of 8); Ravel: Gaspard de la nuit; Milhaud: Sonate; Ravel: Prelude -- Concerto pour la main gauche, arranged for two pianos
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_004_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_004_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_004_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_004_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_004_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_004_01-05pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_004_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_004_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_004_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_004_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_004_01-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 005, 1967-08-11, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1967 Mikhashoff / Original songs Performers: Eleanor Grant, voice; Suzanne Summerville, voice; Mr. Dickinson, voice; Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University of Houston, Ezekiel W. Cullen Auditorium Printed program attached; signed Yvar-Emilian Mikhashoff Requires checking: 01_01 - Portrait of verlaine, for oboe, voice, piano (first bars missing) -- 02_01 Au jardin through 14:11 then Perfumed wasp (1st two songs: Perfumed wasp and Solitude of violet leaves) applause after completion of 2nd song -- 02-02: Perfumed wasp. 3rd song (Pale Fern) -- 02-03: Petals for baritone and piano Derivative files created: 4 (Box 1, Item 5)
    1.875 ips
    Contents: Mikhashoff: Au jardin de l'infante. For Emmanuel Lopez -- Four antique japanese dances -- The perfumed wasp -- Petals from a burnished autumn
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_005_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_005_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_005_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_005_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_005_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_005_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_005_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_005_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_005_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_005_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 006, 1967-05-15, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1967 Senior Recital (UH) incl. Fennimore Performers: Ronald MacKay, piano Recording location: University of Houston, Department of Music Recorded on both sides; Side 2 begins with Debussy Senior recital; given in partial fulfilment of the requirements for the degree Bachelor of Music; printed program attached Requires checking: 01-01: Bartok -- 01-02: Chopin thru Etudes 8? (no applause at end) -- 01-03: Etude no. 12 -- 01_04: Chopin: Nocturne -- doesn't match 01-06: Chopin Etude op. 25 no. 7 Derivative files created: 8 (Box 1, Item 6)
    Contents: Bartók: Improvisations I-VIII; Chopin: Etudes op.25, nos. 1,2,6,7,8,12 -- Prelude op.28, no.24 -- Nocturne op.32, no.1; Debussy: Images. Cloches -- Et la lune -- Poissons d'or; Fennimore: Variations on a theme of Beethoven
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_006_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_006_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_006_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_006_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_006_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_006_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_006_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_006_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_006_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_006_02-02pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_006_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_006_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_006_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_006_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_006_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_006_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_006_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_006_02-02sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 007, 1968-05-20, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1968 Messiaen / Mikhashoff - Traceries Gawain Performers: Jan Cole, flute, recorder, piccolo, alto flute, bass flute; Neil Havens, narrator; Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano, recorder; Barbara Shook, violin; Jerry McCathern, trumpet; Mary Elisabeth Lee, harpsichord; Marian Wilson, violoncello, viola da gamba; Patricia Kennedy, percussion; Yvar Mikhashoff, conductor Recording location: Rice University, Hamman Hall Auditorium Première performances of Traceries and Sir Gawain; printed program for Recital of chamber music by Jan Cole, flutist inserted. It is unclear if the entire program is on the tape and what the spine title reference to Messiaen is about. Requires checking: 4 files for 2 works Derivative files created: 4 (Box 1, Item 7)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: Traceries -- Sir Gawain and the green knight
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_007_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_007_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_007_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_007_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_007_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_007_02-01pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_007_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_007_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_007_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_007_02-01sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 008, 1968-04-24, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1968 Mikhashoff / Seis Caprichos (Ganz) Performers: Mikhashoff, piano; Isabelle Ganz (Lipschutz), soprano Recording location: University of Houston Auditorium number 1, Liberal Arts Building Première performances of Mikhashoff's Seis caprichos and Lipschutz's Next to of course god america; given in partial fulfilment of the requirements for the Master of Music; printed program attached Requires checking: 01_01--01_03 from radio broadcast of Donizetti's Elixir de Amor -- 02_01: Seis caprichos -- 02-02: Lipschutz -- 02_03: unidentified -- 02_04-05 radio broadcast Derivative files created: 8 (Box 1, Item 8)
    Contents: Mikhashoff: Seis caprichos; Weill: Seeräuberjenny; Lipschutz: Next to of course god america; Ives: Soliloquy or a study in 7ths and other things -- Children's hour -- Old home day
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_008_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_008_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_008_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_008_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_008_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_008_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_008_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_008_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_008_02-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_008_02-05pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_008_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_008_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_008_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_008_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_008_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_008_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_008_02-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_008_02-05sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 009, 1968-05-19, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1968 Music of the Twentieth Century (Houston) UH Performers: Yvar-Emilian Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: University of Houston Sticker on reel: "Masters"; pencil inscription on back of container "Seis caprichos"; printed program inserted Same number of files as works Derivative files created: 10 (Box 1, Item 9)
    Contents: Debussy: Etude XI -- La terasse des audiences au clair de lune -- Etude VI; Charpentier: Etudes carnatiques, 3ème cycle; Messiaen: Regard du silence -- Catalogue d'oiseaux: Le loriod; Ginastera: Twelve american preludes, vol.1; Copland: Piano variations; Fennimore: Songs and dances; Prokofiev: Toccata
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_009_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_009_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_009_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_009_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_009_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_009_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_009_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_009_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_009_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_009_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_009_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_009_02-03pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_009_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_009_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_009_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_009_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_009_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_009_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_009_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_009_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_009_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_009_02-03sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 010, 1970-04-21, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1970 Janá?ek, Capriccio - UH Winds and me Performers: Mikhashoff, piano, left hand; Mike White, flute; Jerry McCathern, Billy Parten, trumpet; Wesley Zeagler, Andy Russel, David Vandiver, trombone; Lester Oliver, tenor tuba; Jeffrey Lerner, conductor Recording location: University of Houston, Arnold Hall Edited by Mikhashoff; printed program attached, with only the Jana?ek marked presumably meaning it is the only work on the tape files match movements Derivative files created: 4 (Box 1, Item 10)
    Contents: Janá?ek: Capriccio. I. Allegro -- II. Adagio -- III. Allegretto -- IV. Andante
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_010_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_010_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_010_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_010_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_010_01-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_010_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_010_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_010_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_010_01-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 011, 1970, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1970 Master of Record for flute and Piano Performers: Jan Cole, flute; Mikhashoff, piano Recording location: Unknown location Recorded on both sides; side 2 begins with Faure Master tape for a vinyl record; contents attached to container Requires checking: 7 works, 6 tracks. Carnaval missing Derivative files created: 6 (Box 1, Item 11)
    Contents: Molique: Andante; Blavet: Sonata no.2; Rodrigo: Four songs; Fauré: Sicilienne; Stanley: Solo in D minor, op.1, no.1; Falla: Two songs; Genin: Carnaval de Venise
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_011_01am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_011_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_011_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_011_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_011_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_011_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_011_01-06pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_011_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_011_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_011_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_011_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_011_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_011_01-06sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 012, June 1971?, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1971 Cambiata Concert: Austin in June Performers: Possible performers include: Cambiata Soloists, Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Linda Watson, pianist; Mary Jungerman, clarinet; Amy Winn, flute; Connie Hill, soprano; Frank Dent, speaker; and Mikhashoff, piano, director Recording location: Austin, Texas Contents not clear. Title on spine states June 1971 but program information supplied by initial processor is from a Sunday June 10 concert titled: An afternoon of French music. But, Sunday June 10th occurred in 1973, not 1971. Requires checking: 9 works, 13 files Derivative files created: 13 (Box 1, Item 12)
    Contents: Debussy: Syrinx; Poulenc: Prier pour paix -- "C"; Fennimore: Berlitz songs (excerpts); Ravel: Duet of the child and the princess (L'enfant et les sortileges) -- Ma mère l'oye; Debussy: Des pas sur la neige -- Poissons d'or; Ravel: Histoires naturelle
    Preservation archival master file(s): ubmu0001_4_012_01am.wav, ubmu0001_4_012_02am.wav
    Production master files file: ubmu0001_4_012_01-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_012_01-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_012_01-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_012_01-04pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_012_01-05pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_012_01-06pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_012_01-07pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_012_01-08pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_012_01-09pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_012_02-01pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_012_02-02pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_012_02-03pm.wav, ubmu0001_4_012_02-04pm.wav
    Service copy file: ubmu0001_4_012_01-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_012_01-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_012_01-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_012_01-04sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_012_01-05sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_012_01-06sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_012_01-07sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_012_01-08sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_012_01-09sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_012_02-01sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_012_02-02sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_012_02-03sc.mp3, ubmu0001_4_012_02-04sc.mp3
  - Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Reel to reel tapes, Tape 013, 1972-01-20, 1 7 inch reel; Container title: 1972 Cambiata Soloists: Shakespeare to Strav. Performers: Cambiata soloists, Isabelle Lipschutz, soprano; Mikhashoff, piano, harpsichord, director; David Bonner, flute; James Chamberlain, clarinet; Samuel Thiel, French horn; Harry Clark, violoncello; Rosemary Silversteen, violin; Wolfgang Justen, flute; Phyllis Herdliska, viola; Paul Schmidt, narrator Recording location: Unversity of Texas at Austin, Department of Music Première of Mikhashoff's Four figures; photocopy of printed program inserted 13 works listed, 13 files Derivative files created: 13 (Box 1, Item 13)
    3.75 ips